We'd like you to make a contract with the Devil in this cell.
那就請你跟這個房間裡的惡魔立約
It's the Future Devil.
在裡面的是“未來惡魔”
Two people in Public Safety have a contract with it.
公安裡有兩人與這傢伙訂立契約
One of them gave half their lifespan.
其中一人給了一半的壽命
The other gave it their eyes and their senses of taste and smell.
另一人獻上雙眼、味覺與嗅覺
If it likes you, you might get a better deal.
如果獲得青睞，代價或許會輕一些
There you go.
那麼請進
The future rules.
未來最棒
The future rules…
未來最棒…
CHAINSAW MAN
鏈鋸人
Say it too! The future rules!
快跟我一起大聲喊“未來最棒”
I'm here to make a contract with you.
我是來跟你締結契約的
Tell me what you want from me.
直接說你想得到我的什麼
Your attitude is the worst ever!
你這傢伙是我見過態度最差的！
Whatever. Show me your future!
算了，讓我瞧瞧你的未來吧
The details of a contract depend on the future.
再根據未來，考慮契約內容
Hurry up and stick your head in my belly.
快點把頭放進我的肚子
Otherwise I can't see your future.
不然我看不見你的未來
Here is the contract.
發表契約內容
Let me live in your right eye.
讓我住在你的右眼裡
And I'll help you.
那我就會助你一臂之力
You must be thinking, "That's it?"
瞧你一臉懷疑“那樣就夠了嗎？”
Because you'll die in the worst possible way.
因為你將以最淒慘的方式在未來死去
You must be curious how you'll die.
你想聽聽自己會怎麼死嗎？
-You will-- -Don't bother.
-你會… -不必告訴我
I'm not interested in knowing.
我對自己的死法沒興趣
As long as I can kill those I want to kill,
只要能親手殺了我想殺的目標
I don't care what comes after.
之後怎麼樣都無所謂
Hurry up and get in my eye.
要進眼睛就快點
Okay.
好
I give your moves a perfect score.
剛才的動作有100分
From now on, you don't need to train every day.
今天開始不必每天接受指導了
We'll do it once a week.
改成一週一次
Yay.
萬歲
Great.
太棒了
Keep a cool head even when you get excited.
興奮時也要保持冷靜，動腦思考
Always remember your weapons and the situation.
隨時記得自己的武器與狀況
In light of your training, you'll have real combat tomorrow.
基於指導，明天進行實戰
Real combat?
實戰？
We're going to capture the ones who killed Himeno and others,
我們要出動全員去逮住 殺死姬野等人的武士刀跟蛇女
It'll be the new Division 4's debut.
這是新四課的亮相儀式
If the mission fails, Division 4 will be finished.
萬一作戰失敗，四課就玩完了
And you two will be put down via a real battle with me.
到時你們必須接受處分
If that happens, I'll let you go without killing you.
到時我不會殺了老師，會饒你一命
Because you made me stronger.
因為是你讓我變強了嘛
Now I can kill more Devils.
這樣就能殺死更多惡魔
And if I do that, I'll get a date with Ms. Makima.
然後跟真紀真小姐去約會
Good work. I know you've been quite busy.
百忙之中特地抽空 這次真是辛苦你了
I hope you can keep training Denji and Power.
今後也請多多關照淀治跟帕瓦
I'm sick of them already.
我已經開始厭倦他們了
Every time a dog I trained dies, I drink more alcohol.
每當培育的狗死掉，我喝的酒就更多
I thought I wouldn't feel guilty even if the toys broke…
本來以為玩具壞了 也不會感到一絲的內疚
But my mind's gotten weak with age. I get attached to toys.
但人到了這把年紀就會開始痴呆
So, what did you want to talk about?
然後呢？你要跟我談什麼事？
The ambush on the Special Divisions…
關於這次特異課的遇襲
Public Safety folks are no fools.
公安也不是傻瓜
You knew about it and let it happen, right?
妳明明知情，卻坐視不管吧？
Whatever inhuman things you do, or even if you kill my dogs,
不管妳要做多少喪盡天良的惡行
as long as you're still on the humans' side, I'll leave you alone.
只要妳還跟人類站在同一陣線
Only as long as that's true.
這是前提
All I want is to save as many people from the Devils as possible.
我只是想盡可能 從惡魔手中拯救更多人類
If this mission succeeds,
只要這次的作戰成功
Division 4 will be all over the news.
四課就能在媒體間大量曝光
And then we'll have more freedom to operate
如此一來 四課就會比以往更容易行動
and save more people from the Devils.
也能救更多人不受惡魔傷害
Liar.
騙子
We had the big boss move to the villa.
已經請老大移駕到別墅了
You should go too, sir…
少主也請一起…
As long as Makima's alive, there's nowhere to hide in Japan.
只要真紀真還活著 在日本就無處可躲
Keep quiet.
別吵
Shut up, girl!
女人就乖乖閉嘴！
Sir.
少主
If Grandpa were here, he'd never stand for running away.
假如爺爺還在，絕對不會容許我逃跑
And that damn Denji is in Division 4.
而且該死的淀治就在四課
I have to rip out his heart this time!
我這次一定要挖出他的心臟
No need to worry about your leader.
不必擔心你們家少主
He can be revived anyway.
反正死了也能復活
If you're staying here, worry about not getting bitten instead.
更重要的是，若你們要留下的話
Bitten?
不要被咬？
What does that mean?
這話是什麼意思？
Our secret weapon is underneath.
這裡的下方藏有祕密武器
Grandpa's gift when he died.
是爺爺的遺物
A zombie army made of scum who couldn't pay back their debts.
由沒錢還債的人渣組成的殭屍軍團
Humans bitten by zombies will turn into zombies.
人類被殭屍咬了，就會變成殭屍
That's how we'll finish Division 4.
就用那招終結四課
We're going back to Kyoto once we're done sightseeing.
我們在東京觀光一下就會回京都
We'll probably never see you again.
反正未來應該沒機會見面了
So let me ask you a question.
請讓我問你一個問題吧
I heard you are after the Gun Devil.
我聽說阿秋你的目標是鎗之惡魔
Do you really think you can kill it?
你是真心認為能殺死那傢伙嗎？
You lost to an enemy who killed around 20 members of the Special Division.
面對這次殺死特異課 二十幾人的那傢伙
What makes you think
卻以為自己贏得過 殺死全世界幾百萬人的惡魔？
Our lives were ruined by the Gun Devil too.
其實我們也被鎗之惡魔害得很慘
But we don't even consider killing the Gun Devil.
但我們也沒想過要殺死鎗之惡魔
Anyone in their rational mind knows it's impossible.
只要想一下就知道那是天方夜譚
You are so weak, yet you give yourself a goal like the main character of a manga.
明明弱得要命 卻像漫畫主角一樣滿口雄心壯志
It's so cringy. It gives me goosebumps.
看了就尷尬，還會起雞皮疙瘩
See? I've got them for real.
妳看，真的起雞皮疙瘩了吧？
No.
沒有啊
Keep that gibberish to yourself.
請不要當著我的面講一堆廢話
You just stand back and watch.
你只要安靜看著就好
When I lose and die, you can come laugh at me.
等我打輸死掉了
I'm aware that I'm lost already.
我十分明白自己現在迷失了自我
But…
但是…
I also know that I couldn't go on living if I didn't do this.
我也明白若不這麼做，我就撐不下去
Thank you for the advice.
非常感謝兩位的指導
Aki!
阿秋！
You are one annoying bastard, but I'm rooting for you.
雖然你讓人有夠不爽，但我支持你
I'll give you one last piece of advice.
最後送你這句話
Everyone in the Special Divisions is insane, so watch out.
特異課沒半個正常的傢伙 你要小心點
Our guest is from Public Safety?
是公安的客人啊
Bring us the best tea.
去泡上等的茶招待
Thank you for your cooperation.
謝謝您的合作
Some of our youngbloods went rogue and fired guns in Tokyo.
我底下的小夥子 好像擅自在東京大鬧了一場
I'll answer all your questions.
我什麼問題都願意回答
I hope you can understand that I did not order this hit.
希望妳能明白那些並非我的指示
I heard the one behind it all is this Sawatari girl.
我聽說幕後黑手是這個叫澤渡的女人
This girl's been tricking our youngsters into making a contract with the Gun Devil.
這女人從中牽線
What are the terms of the contract?
告訴我契約的內容
In exchange for 20,000 yen to the Gun Devil,
立約人付給鎗之惡魔兩萬圓
they can get guns and ammo.
就能拿到槍與子彈
Devils need money in their world too, right?
難道惡魔的世界也需要金錢嗎？
They're not so different from humans after all.
簡直跟人類沒兩樣嘛
Please write down the name of everyone who has a contract with the Gun Devil.
請把與鎗之惡魔訂約的所有幫派成員
Oh, sure.
好啊，知道了
Throw them in jail and teach them a lesson.
請送他們去吃一會牢飯，好好反省吧
Not only in your organization.
除了您幫派的成員
I need the names of those from other syndicates too.
其他幫派的人也麻煩一併寫下來
Miss.
這位小姐
You don't have a clue how things work here.
看樣子妳根本什麼都不懂
Even if I knew those names,
即便我真的知情 只要別人發現是我告密
Ridiculous.
妳真傻
It's for the safety of the public.
這是為了保護國民安全
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
請您務必配合
Miss…
小姐
Do you know what necessary evil is?
妳知道所謂的“必要之惡”嗎？
If different organizations go to war with each other,
叫我們自相殘殺看看啊
foreign mafias would find their way into Japan.
到時外國黑手黨就會趁機混入日本
I admit we do some bad things.
我們做的事確實違背正道
But the Chinese and Russian mafias are far worse than us.
但中國或蘇聯的黑手黨 幹的勾當遠比我們更骯髒
We're the ones keeping them out.
我們的存在是防患於未然
Just like that you Devil Hunters keep humans safe from Devils,
就像惡魔獵人從惡魔手中保護人類
we yakuza keep the Japanese people safe from foreigners.
我們黑道也在保護 日本人遠離外國人的威脅
They say many Devil Hunters are uneducated idiots.
惡魔獵人有許多沒學問的笨蛋
So it's natural you wouldn't understand.
難怪不懂這種道理
I won't betray my own for some jump change.
我不會為了小錢出賣同伴
This is not money.
這不是錢
It's everyone here's…
是在場各位所有人的…
fathers', mothers',
父母
grandmothers', grandfathers',
祖母
brothers', sisters',
兄弟姊妹
lovers' or wives'
戀人或妻子的…
eyes.
眼睛
Eyes?
眼睛？
Don't worry.
用不著擔心
We have someone in Public Safety that can put their eyes back.
公安裡有人能讓眼睛恢復原狀
If you can be so kind as to cooperate, I'll introduce them…
只要您願意配合，我就介紹那個人…
You…
妳這臭女人！
The necessary evil you talked about
您剛才所說的必要之惡
is just an excuse to justify your crimes.
只是將自己的惡行正當化的藉口罷了
Our society doesn't need those excuses.
這個社會不需要那種藉口
The truly necessary evils
真正的必要之惡
are always kept collared and controlled by the state.
總是戴著國家的項圈，進行支配
Division 2 and the police have surrounded the basement and the ground floor exits.
對魔二課與警方 包圍了地下室與一樓的入口
Division 4 will be responsible for suppression inside the building.
至於大樓內部則是特異四課負責鎮壓
Kill as many Public Safety members as possible, and take Denji's heart.
盡可能殺光公安，搶走淀治的心臟
At least the two of us should be able to escape afterward if I use the snake.
然後只要使用蛇 應該足夠讓我們兩人逃走
I'll kill Denji.
淀治由我來殺
Don't get too excited.
你別太激動
METROPOLITAN POLICE
（警視廳）
I want to go home.
好想回家
Go home then.
想回去就回去啊
I had training,
因為我做了特訓
so I'll kill that guy with hair on his temples.
我要宰了那個鬢角人
The training even made us smarter.
而且特訓後連頭腦都變好了
Easy peasy.
根本小菜一碟
I want to go home.
好想回家
What's the plan?
有什麼計劃？
There is no plan.
沒有計劃
We're throwing everyone in the Special Division
叫特異課所有人
at that building.
一口氣殺進大樓裡
WATCH OUT FOR EXITING VEHICLES
（出口，出車時請留意）
Excuse me.
不好意思
I'm Furuno from Division 2.
我是對魔二課的古野
I'm the captain of Division 4, Kishibe.
我是特異四課的隊長岸邊
The police and Division 2 will be blocking the ground floor and basement exits.
這次由警方與對魔二課 封鎖一樓與地下出入口
Division 4 will go in to subdue the terrorists.
特異四課進去壓制恐怖分子
There's only one thing you should be aware of.
你們只需要注意一件事
Most of the members in Division 4 are non-humans.
特異四課的隊員幾乎都不是人類
If we let them escape, the damage will be worse than a terrorist attack.
萬一讓他們任何一人跑到大街上
You need to be prepared for a battle against Division 4 as well.
除了恐怖分子
I'll give you the rundown on our members.
我來說明一下隊員的特徵
Zombies…
殭屍…
Eat them all!
吃到飽！
Shark Fiend.
鯊魚魔人
This one can swim on any surface.
牆壁也好，地面也好
The walls, the ground, anything.
他能自由穿梭，游進任何場所
He can take the form of a Devil for a short period.
那傢伙也能短時間變成惡魔
Ouch.
好痛
You tried to bite me, so I thought you were a zombie.
誰叫你要咬我，害我以為你是殭屍
Violence Fiend.
暴力魔人
Normally, they should be weaker as Fiends than they are as Devils.
照理說變成魔人後 會比在惡魔的時候還弱
But this one is still too strong as a Fiend,
但他變成魔人依然強過頭
so we make him wear a poison-dispensing mask.
便給他戴了會放毒的面具
Do not remove that mask under any circumstances.
無論如何都不要摘下他的面具
Hey, lady! You'd better run.
那邊的小姐，我勸妳快逃
You'll turn into a zombie if you get bitten.
人類被咬了會變成殭屍喔
Oh, you're a Devil.
搞什麼？原來是惡魔
Spider Devil.
蜘蛛惡魔
She usually takes a human shape.
平常主要維持人類外型
Devils with humanlike appearances tend to be friendly to humans,
外表酷似人類的惡魔會對人類較友善
but a Devil's a Devil.
但惡魔就是惡魔
She kills people when she's mad.
一發飆就會殺人
You got my shoes dirty.
鞋子髒掉了
What a jerk.
這傢伙爛透了
Angel Devil.
天使惡魔
This one is special.
這傢伙是特別的惡魔
A Devil who's not hostile toward humans. But do not approach.
對人類沒有敵意，但還是別靠近
Touch this one and your lifespan gets absorbed.
因為一碰到那傢伙，壽命就會被吸走
Hey, you. Got a handkerchief?
那邊的人
Why do you get so close to me?
你居然敢靠近我
Your life will be shortened if you touch me.
碰到我的話，你的壽命會縮短耶
Not through cloth, right?
隔著布就沒差吧
That one hurt.
好痛喔
Devil! Move him outside!
惡魔，把這傢伙搬到外面去
You're ordering me around.
竟敢命令我
Well, still better than fighting, I guess.
算了，至少不是叫我戰鬥
You guys.
你們幾個
Leave this to the Fiends.
這裡交給那群魔人
We're going after Katana Man and the snake girl.
我們去找武士刀跟蛇女
No.
不知道
We'll go separately.
分頭找出來
Surrender now--
乖乖投降…
Snake.
蛇
Spit it out.
吐出來
Son of a…
妳這個混帳
Ghost.
幽靈
Kill him.
殺死那傢伙
Your moves have improved.
動作變得更靈活了嘛
If you use my power,
只要利用我的力量
your right eye will see a sliver into the future.
你的右眼就能看見稍遠的未來
But that's all.
可惜只是看得見而已
Strangle him to death.
直接掐死他